Please? We won't make it
in time for the festival.
I still can't allow you
to stay on campus overnight.
Do we pull an all-nighter
at somebody's place?
If none of your places work...
Pretty spacious, Mayama.
I'm ready to work all night.
I'm sorry we imposed.
We all invited ourselves over, day of.
It's fine.
I want our haunted house to be a success.
In middle school,
my friends often made fun of me.
Dude, obviously we were joking.
She'd never confess to a guy like you.
- Exactly!
- To them,
it was all a joke.
Asamiya. I'm happy you told me how you felt.
And I want to believe you, I really do.
But I can't help it. I'm still scared.
So, could you wait?
I'll wait as long as you need me to.
And don't feel forced to answer, either.
When you have a break during the festival,
do you want to check out
the other set-ups together?
Yeah. I want to eat crepes.
Sounds good.
Mayama?
[Tenn Mayama (Esteemed brother)]
Hello?
Asamiya?
Good morning.
I'm sorry, Hare can't make it
to the festival today.
Huh?
[Kitahara High Culture Festival]
- Looks good.
- Let me grab a pic.
[Haunted House]
Grab our supplies.
Thanks.
[Haunted House]
Yikes. Keep it up!
Where's Mayama?
Did you hear anything from him?
No.
Maybe he overslept?
- He's not you, you know.
- Hey!
Tell Haru I told him to rest up.
We'll handle things just fine.
Sorry, I know it's sudden.
No worries at all.
Wait.
Asamiya...
Please don't tell anyone I'm sick.
Huh?
I'll do something about it.
What do you mean?
We've got a line forming.
Guess we'll have to start without Mayama.
Are we using this Dracula costume?
Nah. Put it in storage for now.
- Sure.
- Wait.
If...
If Mayama doesn't show...
I'll...
Sorry I'm late.
Asamiya, you handle the rest, okay?
- Sure.
- All right.
Who was that guy anyway?
Beats me.
One of our helpers?
Did you go see a doctor?
Yeah.
I also took some medicine, so I'm fine now.
Huh?
You're still a bit warm.
Don't push yourself, okay?
But...
It's not your fault you're sick.
I'll tell the others what's going on.
I want to push through.
We all worked so hard on this.
Try them on.
Scare you?
If I push through till the end,
I think I'll come to like myself a bit more.
So, please.
Make a face like that,
and you know I can't stop you.
Fine. But I have one condition.
What is it?
Leave enough strength
to go around the festival with me.
Of course.
I promised, didn't I?
[Haunted House]
[CAUTION]
Looking good, Mayama.
You're paving new frontiers for werewolves.
Am I supposed to be happy about that?
Can I snag a pic?
Sure.
All right. Let's do this.
- Right.
- Come in.
You too, Mayama.
Repeat after me.
Ready? Victory!
- Victory?
- Victory...
I guess?
Don't sound so skeptical.
Why, "victory"?
It was the first word I thought of.
Pick a better word next time.
Hey, rude!
- Quit pestering me about it!
- I'm just saying.
Hello there!
Thanks for coming!
Please take a pamphlet.
No way, no way.
There's definitely something here.
I can sense it.
I'm scared already!
Oh my gosh.
- Do you see something?
- I think so.
- Did that doll move?
- Maybe?
Roar!
Louder.
Yes, ma'am.
I think he's loud enough.
Definitely not.
Trust me, I'm a former theater kid.
Just a minute, we're almost ready!
Now, repeat after me.
Roar!
- Roar.
- Roar!
[Entrance]
Roar!
Great work, team!
[Haunted House on break until 1 P.M.]
Great work.
Our haunted house is a hit on social media.
People are especially praising our werewolf.
Yeah, you're doing great, Mayama!
You upped your game by the end there.
Thanks.
- Mayama?
- I'm fine.
Just got a bit dizzy.
Since when?
You're going to the infirmary.
I'm fine. I just need to take more medicine.
You need to treat yourself better.
Is he feeling sick?
Yeah. Cover for me until I'm back.
No...
I have to get back.
Leave the rest to us, Mayama.
You awake?
The haunted house...
The festival's over.
Asamiya told us you were sick.
Sorry we didn't notice.
We must've been pushing you.
Oh...
It's over.
I see.
Even though...
Not the time.
Aw, no practice?
We all worked so hard...
I ruined it.
It's my fault.
I'm so sorry.
Nothing was "ruined".
- Huh?
- If anything, we had a roaring success.
Thanks to a last minute, first-rate helper.
Helper?
Asamiya...
You're awake.
Glad to see you're okay.
Did you step in for me?
Dracula-Asamiya brought in
a crazy amount of customers.
What?
- Wait, he's super hot.
- Oh my god!
He totally is!
He's so good-looking!
We wanted Asamiya to inherit
your role as werewolf.
But he insisted the werewolf
was your role alone.
Of course. I could never surpass
such perfect casting.
Should we leave you to it?
- Yeah.
- We're heading out already?
Duh. We have to finish cleaning up.
Come on.
Thanks for covering for me.
Just worry about yourself for now.
Mayama?
I really am useless after all.
I'm sure you didn't enjoy
getting dressed up for people, either.
This was the least I could do for you.
Besides, now I know what it's like
to act for someone else.
It's like I was in your shoes for once.
Were you okay with me taking your place?
You should lie down.
Sorry.
Let me stay like this.
The Dracula in me...
May lose his control.
Dracula only acts at night.
That sort of logic doesn't apply
to Amamiya-Dracula.
I know you don't mean it.
You're always considerate of my feelings.
I'm always your priority.
While you were at the doctor's this morning,
I received a call from your older brother.
I'm sorry for all the trouble.
It's fine. I'm more worried about Haru.
I think Haru will go,
no matter what the doctor says.
Did you hear about his time in middle school?
A bit.
Our parents are often out the house for work,
and Haru never feels like he can talk to me.
So, I'm really grateful to you, Asamiya.
I haven't done anything though.
Haru really seems to be
enjoying himself these days.
Which is exactly why
he's afraid he'll end up alone again.
I can tell he's desperate
to live up to everyone's expectations.
Don't force yourself
to live up to expectations.
Don't put yourself down, either.
Since that day we changed seats,
and I decided to confess to you,
I've gotten to know you much better.
I also know what you consider your faults.
But all that has made me
fall for you even more.
So...
Please don't ever think lowly of yourself.
Mayama?
Are you still asleep?
We have to close up school soon.
I'll be coming in, okay?
Were you awake?
Yes.
How do you feel?
Can you get home by yourself?
Ms. Komori.
Your face...
I helped fill in your shoes, too.
Scaring guests was just so much fun!
I see.
Now get yourself home, all right?
Yes, ma'am.
You okay?
Yeah, I'll manage.
What?
I forgot to take a video of your werewolf.
I only took a picture.
A picture's worth a thousand words, right?
Let's go.
I want to touch him.
I want to monopolize that expression of his.
Let's go around
the festival together next year.
Yeah. You'd better.
I guess I'll take the video next year.
A haunted house, two years in a row?
Really?
I think I'm ready.
I'm finally ready
to give Asamiya my answer.
See you tomorrow.
And one more thing, Mayama.
You don't have to come to like me, okay?
Huh?
I was satisfied enough confessing to you.
I won't ask for anything more.
- But...
- Besides,
you're lovable to me
like a local mascot would be.
Nothing more than that.
What the heck?
I was serious.
Mayama?
Whatever.
Welcome home.
How are you feeling?
Haru?
What do you mean, a mascot?
It was all a big misunderstanding?
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Now I've fallen for you for real.
I should've known.
Of course Asamiya wasn't serious about me.
You gotta give it one more push, Mayama.
Who's ready to sing?
- What's going on?
- Isn't that obvious?
This is a mixer.
I wanted to stay by your side
all summer, Mayama.
You're being unfair.
If your feelings are a mess, tell him.
He'll understand.
What I want isn't so simple, though.
Go home.
You're the one
who drew the line first, Asamiya.
You're going through a tough romance, buddy.
Tell me the truth.
Did you do this sort of thing with Sakaki?